etihadguest.com 2017-06-17

# Privacy policy - Etihad Guest

### Information we collect

#### Membership

When you join Etihad Guest, we willcollect details from you to set up your Etihad Guest account and allow you to start collecting and spending reward points. This willinclude your name, date of birth and contact details _(such as your address, email and phone number),_ details of any linked family accounts, along with other information. We will also ask you to set up a user name and password.

 _Where you are asking us to link family members to a single account, it is your responsibility to ensure each family member understands how we will use their personal information and obtain their consent to using their details in accordance with this Privacy Policy. We will assume that you have done this.Our website is not directed towards children. If you are creating Etihad Guest membership for an individual less than 13 years of age,you are providing us your affirmative parental consent as the legal parent or guardian to collect, use and process the information of the individual less than 13 years of age, consistent with this Privacy Policy. You can always manage personal information and contact preferences you provided to us via the Etihad Guest Website. If you need any additional information, please use the contact information provided in this Privacy Policy to contact us._

#### Personalized account

We may invite you to provide additional information about your travel preferences, next of kin, dietary requirements, personal interests and any related reward scheme memberships that you may have. You don't need to provide this information to open an account, but it helps us to provide a more personalized service and makes it quicker to process travel bookings and mileage redemptions. 

#### Earning and Redeeming miles

If you make a qualifying purchase with Etihad Airways or one of our other carefully-chosen network of international and local travel, financial services, leisure and lifestyle [partners](http://www.etihadguest.com/en/earn-miles/) (" **Partners** "), or otherwise quote your membership of the Etihad Guest programme, they will provide information to us about the purchase or card activity so we can log it to your account. We do this to ensure you are awarded appropriate miles, help the Partner to validate any benefits you are claiming as well as other service delivery and marketing purposes. If you have an Etihad co-branded credit card, debit card or another financial product, we will also collect and process transactional and activity data associated with such products.

Together with our Partners, we offer you the chance to redeem your miles through our Reward Shop. Where you choose to redeem miles through the Reward Shop, we may ask you for additional information to redeem the benefit. In many cases, we will transfer you to the Partner to complete the relevant transaction. For example, if you choose to redeem miles for a holiday offered by Etihad Holidays, once you have claimed the miles on the Reward Shop, we will put you in touch with Etihad Holidays who will then make arrangements to complete the holiday booking.

Any additional information that has been provided to complete a redemption will be governed by the terms and conditions and privacy policy of the relevant merchant who is responsible for providing the product or service which you are purchasing through the Reward Shop. Merchant details _(including any terms and conditions)_ are clearly displayed at the point of redemption.

#### Events and promotions

From time to time we hold events and special promotions to introduce Etihad Guest to new members. If you come to one of these events, or take part in a promotion, we may ask for your personal details to help us run the promotion and keep in touch with you about Etihad Guest services that think may be of interest to you. Any information which you provide will be kept in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy and you can unsubscribe from further communications from us at any time.

#### Customer support and online services

If you contact us with a query or comment about any of our services, or would like us to keep you informed about latest news and developments at Etihad Guest, we will need to collect information about you _(including your contact details)_ to help us respond to your query or request. We may do this when you can call our customer support centre, or interact with us through our online support tools.

We may also keep a record of any communications we have with you _(including a recording of any calls you make)_. We do this to help monitor and improve the quality of our customer support services along with other research, marketing and promotional activities. Where you have asked to receive an information update from us, you are free to change your preferences.

#### Other personal information

We collect personal information about you from many channels about activities like your travels, purchases, and interests to provide compelling services and relevant marketing and promotional offers to you. We may also automatically collect information from your computer and devices, including real-time geo-location information to provide you with relevant services and offers. We may also use variety of technologies, such as cookies, web beacons and other internet and mobile technologies to collect information about you on websites and our mobile app. We may also collect social media information from your interaction with our social media channels.In order to provide you with the most relevant offers and information, we may partner with third party agencies, Partners and group companies to collect additional information about you. 

### How we use personal information

We will store, process, use and transfer personal information to provide you services and offers, including,but not limited to:

  * to fulfil the terms of any agreement we have with you, including to accrue mileage to your Etihad Guest account, validate your tier status and manage your account;
  * to allow you to register on the Etihad Guest Websites and administer and personalize any of the online services which you have asked us to provide to you;
  * to keep you notified of your account status, including to tell you about any important changes to the Etihad Guest programme;
  * to keep you informed about products and services which we and our Partners and group companies offer where we think you will find this valuable;
  * to allow you to take part in any contest or other promotional offers;
  * to analyse how our users access and navigate the Etihad Guest services and use of Etihad Guest Websites and mobile apps;
  * to get feedback on the quality of our services - we may invite you to participate in questionnaires or surveys;
  * to help detect and prevent abuse, fraud and criminal activity; 
  * to help in marketing, promotional, research and analytical purposes; 
  * to personalize and target content and offers onEtihad Guest Website, mobile app, Partner and group company websites and other websites; and
  * for any other purpose notified on the Etihad Guest Website from time to time.

#### How we share information with others

We work closely with a number of trusted Partners and group companies with whom we share personal information routinely. These include:

  * our group companies and affiliates around the world, including other Etihad brands such as Etihad Airways and Etihad Holidays and non-Etihad brands
  * Partners, to validate your entitlement to miles and enable redemption of miles;
  * Partners, to tell you about special benefits, marketing and promotional offers as well as research and analytics;
  * Partners, to deliver Etihad Guest benefits that you have asked them to provide to you, such as priority boarding, upgrades, lounge access;
  * Partners, for marketing, promotional, research and analytical purposes;
  * banks and payment providers, to authorize and complete payments, detect fraud and misuse, as well as for marketing and promotional purposes;
  * service providers who work with us to help provide our services, including local agents who help manage customer needs at airports or operate our limousine service, and contractors who help us run our office operations;
  * companies whom we transfer or may transfer our rights and duties under our agreement with you;
  * other agencies, law enforcement or governmental organisations for prevention of crime, fraud, misuse or any other compliance related purposes or
  * our contractors and agents to do any of the above on our behalf.

#### How we protect your information

We invest in industry standard technologies and processes for protecting the security of personal information. For instance,

  * We offer the use of secure communication transmission software (known as "secure sockets layer" or "SSL") that encrypts all information you input to our website before it is sent to us. SSL is an industry standard encryption protocol and this ensures that the information is reasonably protected against unauthorised interception;
  * We also follow industry standardsecurity procedures in the storage and disclosure of information, which you have given us, to prevent unauthorised access to that information; and We take reasonable steps to protect your personal information but cannot guarantee the security of any data you disclose to us via email or online. 

We take reasonable steps to protect your personal information but cannot guarantee the security of any data you disclose to us via email or online. 

### More about direct marketing

We are committed to keeping you informed about our and Partner’s products and services in line with your personal preferences. You can change your preferences at any time _(see below)_.

### Updating your personal profile and preferences

At any time you can update your personal profile, or change your preferences for the way in which you would like usto communicate with you - including how you receive news updates from us, or details of our latest offers.

If you have an online account, the easiest way to do this is by logging into your account and changing your personal details, [click here](http://www.etihadguest.com/en/your-account/update-profile/). You can also click the "unsubscribe" link that you will find on any online newsletters, which you receive, or contact our customer support team by sending email to [guest@etihadguest.com](mailto:guest@etihadguest.com). 

### Accessing your personal information

Much of the personal information we hold about you is accessible from Etihad Guest Website. In some countries, you have the right to accessthe personal information we hold about you. We may charge a small fee for processing this request. To receive a copy, please write to Etihad Guest, PO Box 35566, Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates or email [guest@etihadguest.com](mailto:guest@etihadguest.com). If you are concerned that any of the information we hold about you is incorrect, please contact us so that we can amend our records. 

### International Transfer of your personal information

We need to transfer personal information across the Etihad group of companies to help operate our business efficiently as well as our Partners and affiliates for various purposes outlined in this privacy policy. We also allow third party service providers to process personal information where this is needed in connection with a service they provide to us. These arrangements will involve your personal information being located in various countries around the world, including in the United Arab Emirates (UAE) where we have our head offices.

You need to be aware that different privacy laws may apply in these countries from any laws that may apply in the country where you are located. _By accepting the terms and conditions of the Etihad Guest programme, you are providing us your affirmative consent to transfer your personal data cross border and internationally._ We will always strive to adopt the industry standards of information protection, wherever your personal information is located.

### Updates

We keep this Privacy Policy under regular review and place updates on the Etihad Guest Websites from time to time. Please review this Privacy Policy periodically for changes. Any changes will apply retroactively to any personal data that has already been collected. Your continued use of our website or services once you have been notified of the revised Privacy Policy constitutes your acceptance of it.

### Our policy on "cookies"

A cookie is an element of data that a website sends to your browser, which then stores it on your system. Cookies allow us to understand who has seen which pages and advertisements, to determine how frequently particular pages are visited and to determine the most popular areas of our website. Cookies also allow us to make Etihad Guest Websites more user-friendly by, for example, allowing us to take you to the language site of last use, so that we can give you a better experience when you return to our website.

A cookie will be deployed on your device when you visit Etihad Guest Websites unless you indicate that you do not wish this to happen or if you have turned this feature 'off' in your web browser settings. For more information about how our cookies work and information about how to manage your cookie settings please visit our [Cookie Policy](http://www.etihadguest.com/en/terms-and-conditions/).

### Other websites

Etihad Guest Websites and mobile apps may link you to other websites (including [Etihad website](http://www.etihad.com/?CID=ema:gst:web_privacypolicypage_revenuelinkjul16:guestsenen:etihadguest:allsegments:&utm_campaign=web_privacypolicypage_revenuelinkjul16&utm_medium=Web&utm_source=guestsenen&utm_content=etihadguest), [Etihad Airways website](http://www.etihad.com/?CID=ema:gst:web_privacypolicypage_revenuelinkjul16:guestsenen:etihadguest:allsegments:&utm_campaign=web_privacypolicypage_revenuelinkjul16&utm_medium=Web&utm_source=guestsenen&utm_content=etihadguest), [Etihad Holidays website](http://www.etihad.com/en-ae/etihad-holidays/)). We are not responsible for the way in which third party websites operate or the way in which they may process any personal information, which you provide to them. It is important that you understand this and check their respective privacy policies and terms of use. 

### Comments and queries

If you have any comments or queries in connection with our privacy policy, please [**click here**](http://www.etihadguest.com/en/contact-us/).

#### Contact Information

Etihad Guest LLC

PO Box 35566, Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates

International Phone numbers, please [click here](http://www.etihadguest.com/en/contact-us/)

### Terms and Conditions

Please [click here](http://www.etihadguest.com/en/terms-and-conditions/) to view the Etihad Guest membership terms and conditions.
